{
    "id": "f420cc8894034e408dee4f6675ad5ea3",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I look forward to ………………. my grandchildren.",
            "description": "When to is used as a preposition, it is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "see"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13adc059621d417f96b175c53ae52525"
        },
        {
            "question": "They accused him …………………… poisoning their dog.",
            "description": "We accuse somebody of something.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "705c322166a344db8b5f478743c116cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I totally disagree …………………….. you.",
            "description": "We agree with a person.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5b6d61affa79447b80d4a47755eb04e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot agree ……………………… the argument that a ban on smoking violates individual rights.",
            "description": "We agree with an opinion or argument.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "62548d03b4324b008134271437e3edcb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must apologize …………………….. my rude conduct.",
            "description": "We apologize for something.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0cb9232fa354e6e98a8fc09b14a13c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "They will take you back if you apologize ……………………….. them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21678e3034564a6f853cfd571b9f0804"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe ………………………… ghosts?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "01e993b6ef2249448688c100c9683bd1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The loud noise from the street prevented me ……………………… sleeping.",
            "description": "Prevent is followed by from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0644a46dbb564741ae9601f57538f0cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was quite impressed …………………… her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f774fe7ba38b485181f0f5dcbafc2262"
        },
        {
            "question": "You don’t have to pay …………………… that drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76c29798cc7440798cee6a60654d7bb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Once he found a good job, he got married …………………….. his childhood sweetheart.",
            "description": "Marriage is used with the preposition to.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "106e4d7e7ab344b288ffe9fc176250ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know the reason ……………………… his unhappiness.",
            "description": "Reason is followed by for.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "926cf3d652a642b3afca949e2bab638c"
        }
    ]
}